[{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664040836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":17387,"timeElapsed":94351},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664083744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":42907,"timeElapsed":137259},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664089958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6212,"timeElapsed":143473},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664106289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":16329,"timeElapsed":159804},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664110276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3985,"timeElapsed":163791},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664118025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7748,"timeElapsed":171540},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664121404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3377,"timeElapsed":174919},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664132155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":10749,"timeElapsed":185670},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664139491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7334,"timeElapsed":193006},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4920,"timeElapsed":199195},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664148228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2545,"timeElapsed":201743},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664150924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2695,"timeElapsed":204439},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664155622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4697,"timeElapsed":209137},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664160591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4967,"timeElapsed":214106},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664163918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3325,"timeElapsed":217433},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664166626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2707,"timeElapsed":220141},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664172648,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6019,"timeElapsed":226163},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664179030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":6380,"timeElapsed":232545},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":14509,"timeElapsed":247056},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664204453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":9914,"timeElapsed":257968},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664209754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5301,"timeElapsed":263269},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3926,"timeElapsed":267196},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5988,"timeElapsed":273185},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":16590,"timeElapsed":289776},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664240924,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4661,"timeElapsed":294439},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5637,"timeElapsed":300078},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664251276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4712,"timeElapsed":304791},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664257354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6076,"timeElapsed":310868},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664259988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2633,"timeElapsed":313503},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7443,"timeElapsed":322391},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4130,"timeElapsed":326522},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4441,"timeElapsed":330964},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3715,"timeElapsed":334681},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664283920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2752,"timeElapsed":337435},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4803,"timeElapsed":342238},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664290986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2263,"timeElapsed":344501},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3922,"timeElapsed":348425},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664296841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1930,"timeElapsed":350356},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4551,"timeElapsed":356013},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664305367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2868,"timeElapsed":358882},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2212,"timeElapsed":361096},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5736,"timeElapsed":366834},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4682,"timeElapsed":371518},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":375487},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664325614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3640,"timeElapsed":379129},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3576,"timeElapsed":382707},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2429,"timeElapsed":385136},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":9324,"timeElapsed":395607},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3086,"timeElapsed":398695},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664348253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3071,"timeElapsed":401768},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3001,"timeElapsed":404771},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664354155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2899,"timeElapsed":407670},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664357114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2958,"timeElapsed":410629},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3516,"timeElapsed":414148},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4881,"timeElapsed":419031},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1963,"timeElapsed":420995},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":5474,"timeElapsed":427432},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2744,"timeElapsed":430177},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2305,"timeElapsed":432483},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2277,"timeElapsed":434761},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664383021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1773,"timeElapsed":436536},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664385400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2378,"timeElapsed":438915},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664387600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2200,"timeElapsed":441115},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3154,"timeElapsed":444271},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1984,"timeElapsed":446257},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4620,"timeElapsed":451911},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2885,"timeElapsed":454798},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664404069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2785,"timeElapsed":457584},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664406665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2595,"timeElapsed":460180},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2657,"timeElapsed":462838},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":465885},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664414526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2155,"timeElapsed":468041},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664417060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2532,"timeElapsed":470575},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664418806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1745,"timeElapsed":472321},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":15794,"timeElapsed":489390},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4481,"timeElapsed":493873},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":495987},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664444809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2337,"timeElapsed":498324},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2006,"timeElapsed":500331},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":503828},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664452331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2016,"timeElapsed":505846},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664454688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2356,"timeElapsed":508203},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1895,"timeElapsed":510099},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664462267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4882,"timeElapsed":515782},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664465257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2988,"timeElapsed":518772},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664467426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2167,"timeElapsed":520941},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664473022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5594,"timeElapsed":526537},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664474970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1946,"timeElapsed":528485},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664477152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":530667},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664479245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2092,"timeElapsed":532760},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664481383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2136,"timeElapsed":534898},{"subjectID":"7pqb7ax2lo","prolificID":"66805f486ae4ada5289839e3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421414241f4403eeecadc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664484329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2945,"timeElapsed":537844}]